- Chris, did you get your homework done?
- Yup.
Chris, I know
when you're lying to me.
Just like Santa Claus knows
when you're sleeping.
What was that?
Hey, what the hell?
Uh, hey.
- Get out of here!
- Okay, okay!
No, Mom. I got it all done.
For my science homework,
I had to make
a shoebox diarrhea of the evolution of man.
You mean diorama?
Uh-oh.
Hey, Lois,
I got your pregnancy test.
What the hell
you need this for?
I need it
because I think I might be pregnant.
What? My God,
are you sure it's yours?
Lois pregnant?
I didn't think the fat man still had that
kind of marksmanship.
But that's what they said
about Lee Harvey Oswald.
Hey, Mr. President!
Mr. President, up here!
I voted for you!
Wait a minute.
That guy on the grassy knoll's
got a gun.
He's gonna
shoot the President.
Holy smokes,
I've got to do something.
All right, Lee.
Time to become
an American hero.
Okay, one more minute,
and then if there are two pink lines...
Oh, God, I hope
you're not pregnant.
We can't afford another kid.
We already got Chris,
Stewie, Richie,
Joanie, Greg, Marcia,
Bobby, Jan,
Mike Seaver, Carol Seaver,
Boner, Urkel, Mr. Furley...
Peter, those aren't
your kids.
That's the
Nick at Nite lineup.
Blanka, Zangief,
Chun-Li, Guile, E. Honda...
That's Street Fighter.
Red, blue, green.
Those are colors.
God, I can't believe
we weren't more careful.
This probably
happened that night we tried role-playing.
Oh, I need a spanking.
I'm a bad, bad girl.
I'm a paladin
with 18 charisma and 97 hit points.
I can use my helm
of disintegration and do one-D-four damage
as my half-elf mage wields
his plus-five holy avenger.
Paladins can't use
the helm of disintegration.
Oh. Okay,
then I'm a black guy.
Oh, thank God.
It's negative.
Ooh. Dodged a bullet there, right?
Although, I got to tell you,
I was kind of getting
used to the idea
of having a little
brother or sister.
Peter, we can't risk
these things anymore.
You're absolutely right.
Lois, you're getting
your tubes tied.
Why should I
get my tubes tied?
You should
get a vasectomy.
First of all,
I don't know what that is,
and, second of all,
no freaking way.
Peter, it's the
male equivalent
of a woman
getting her tubes tied,
except, it's actually
a lot quicker and safer.
Let these guys explain.
Well, I'm starting
to get the picture, but how's it done?
Lois, I know how to settle
our vasectomy dispute.
A no-rules funny car race
from here to Boston.
Last one to Fenway
gets snipped.
Peter, what the hell?
Where did these things
come from?
They were Loretta's.
Please take them,
they are no longer
funny to me.
Go!
Almost there.
Eat my dust, Lois.
Well, it looks like
I'm a man with no sperm.
But I'll always be a man
with no sperm
who once had a wonderful day.
Well, guys,
my vasectomy is tomorrow.
You poor bastard.
After all, sex is pointless
without potency.
That's right. You take the venom
out of a cobra and what do you got?
You got a, a belt.
It's not that
big a deal.
A bunch of the guys
on the force have had vasectomies,
and their lives
haven't changed at all.
Would you ever have one?
Never!
Well, yeah. But what if me and Lois
do end up wanting another baby?
Lt'll be too late.
You could freeze
some of your sperm
at the sperm bank just in case.
I don't know, Cleveland.
It didn't work out so great
that time I froze my nuts.
No! No! Bad squirrel.
Those are my nuts. My nuts!
You're just
a hungry little fellow, aren't you?
But those are my nuts!
No. Oh, God, no!
My nuts! My nuts!
- Hey, Brian. You want to play tag?
- No.
- Freeze tag?
- TV tag?
- No.
If I can get some guys
you want to play Red Rover?
No. Maybe.
You get the guys first.
We'll talk about it.
No! Jungle gym mine!
Hey, where'd you get
the Pete Rose haircut?
Anyone else want to feel
my Weebok in their grapes?
Then you'll all do as I say.
- Hi.
- Well, hello there.
Yes, that's right, cry.
Cry like Sauron when he lost
his contact lens.
Nobody move! Nobody move!
Does anybody see it?
It might be stuck
to a tree or a rock.
Anyone?
Oh, I am so grounded.
Hi, there. Peter Griffin.
I've got an appointment
to, uh, banish a White Russian
from my Kremlin.
Well, we don't have empty rooms
right now, but if you'll have a seat...
Yeah. I kind of
warmed myself up
in the car
if you catch my drift.
- I could put you in the storage freezer.
- That'll work.
Nurse, I've got a splinter.
Just come out
whenever you're done.
Oh, God! Oh, God! Oh, God!
Oh, God! I...
I think I feel them moving.
Hi. My partner and I
want to have a baby.
We'd like a vial of sperm
and an applicator
that looks like Jodie Foster's knuckles.
Certainly. Let me
just go to the freezer.
Mr. Griffin,
you were in there an awfully long time.
- Are you all right?
- Yup, yup. Fine, fine.
And just so you know,
everything in there
is exactly the way
it was when I went in.
There is absolutely
zero chance that I spilled all the jars
and had to refill them
with my own sperm.
Zero chance.
It's a boy!
Victory shall be mine!
We now return to Tony Danza
and Sylvester Stallone in What?
Peter, we have to talk.
We haven't had sex
since your vasectomy.
Yeah, I just don't
feel like it, Lois,
seeing as how I'm
not a real man anymore.
Honey, it was just
a simple operation.
It's no reason to
give up on your sex life.
I don't know, Lois.
I'm just not feeling it anymore.
Besides, it gives me time
to try new things,
like that time I tried
wearing adult diapers.
Hey, Lois. Hey, kids.
Oh, boy,
that smells delicious.
You know, I'd love to stay
and eat with you,
but I got to go meet
Cleveland, Joe, and Quagmire down at...
the bar.
So just put my dinner
in the fridge
and I'll heat it up later.
Love you.
You, go get me an ice cream.
You, clear the slide.
I'm going down
in five minutes.
You! Did you get me
my Cheez Whiz, boy?
You're my boyfriend.
Yes, dear. Of course I am.
Now, where's Lloyd
with our Fun Dip?
Good God! Running an empire
is harder than finding diversity
in the Abercrombie & Fitch catalog.
Ooh! Ooh! There he is.
There he is. Right there.
Ah, found him.
That was a tricky one.
No kidding. He looks weird.
What the deuce is
all the commotion?
All right.
Out of my way. Move aside.
What the hell is so
bloody fascinating?
You!
Well, well, well.
If it isn't my
half brother Stewie!
Bertram! I haven't
seen you since our microscopic encounter.
How the deuce
did you get out of Peter's testicles?
- He donated sperm.
- Gross.
Well, I don't mean
to be a discourteous host,
but this is my playground.
I rule this territory.
My, my! What an amusingly
misguided view.
Very well, then. You leave me
no choice but to declare war!
So be it. I'll do to you
what B.C. does to comedy on a daily basis.
Hey, why is Juan so happy?
I think he finally figured himself out.
Huh, I guess it takes Juan to know Juan.
Hey, boys. You having
a midnight snack?
- Hmm.
- Mmm-hmm.
I'm just gonna
grab something, too, and go back to bed
alone again.
Night.
You know, Lois
has gotten kind of fat
since you guys
stopped having sex.
It might be
time to, you know, have some sex.
You know, at first I didn't want to do it
'cause of the vasectomy.
But now it's just...
I mean, look at her.
She's got elbow cleavage.
You know, that little wrinkle
that fat people get on their elbows
that looks like a schwa?
I mean, you wouldn't have
sex with her, would you?
- Oh, yeah, I would.
- Really?
Oh, yeah. Oh, yeah.
I would do everything to her.
I don't care
what she looks like.
I would wreck that chick.
Well, you are a trouper.
Sorry. Fat wife
coming through.
Sorry. Sorry.
Excuse me. Fat wife.
Oh, hold on a sec.
All right, bring her through.
Peter, stop it.
For God's sake,
you're embarrassing me.
Not as embarrassed
as I was
when I got that job
entertaining prison inmates.
Do it again, Griffin.
Come on. I just did it,
like, five times.
Do it!
Look, honey,
with all due respect,
you've gained
some weight recently.
It's five pounds at the most.
It's not a big deal.
It's a slippery slope, Lois. You start with
five pounds and then one day, boom!
You wake up and you're on The Practice
with 16 rings in your ear.
You're one to talk.
Look how fat you are.
Lois, men aren't fat.
Only fat women are fat.
Now, if you'll excuse me, I have to go
warn the chef that you've arrived.
He wants fat?
I'll show him fat.
The only reason
I'm eating anyway is because of him.
He won't touch me.
Do you think I'm fat?
Only if you think
I'm a serial killer.
- What?
- Nothing.
Attention, all hands.
We're going to launch
a massive air strike
against Bertram
and his army.
Behold the armada.
It's quite simple, actually.
You press the smiling duck
to take off,
the cow with the bow
tie to fire weapons,
and the clown face
is just a clown face. Enjoy it.
Now, battle stations,
everyone!
At my signal, unleash hell!
What took you so long?
What took you so ugly?
Well, now what?
- You want to play 20 questions?
- Sure.
- Uh, is it a man?
- Yes.
- Is he famous?
- Is he under 40?
- No.
- Over 40?
- Yes.
- On television?
- On television now?
- No.
- In the past 20 years?
- Yes.
- Is it Richard Mulligan?
- Yes!
Up until now,
we've been fighting Bertram on his terms.
Whoa, easy.
Easy, girl. Easy, easy, easy.
But I propose an invasion.
We've got to
fight him over there by the swing set
so we don't have to
fight him here at the sandbox.
Stewie?
What's this?
A letter of surrender.
We did it.
Whew! It's a good thing,
too, because
I really didn't
have an exit strategy.
Yay, Stewie!
Oh, thank you, darling. I...
What is this? Makeup?
Why are you wearing makeup?
Chicken pox!
Damn you, Bertram.
I thought we called no biological warfare.
You swore on the seesaw.
Stewie, there you are.
Oh, my God. Your face.
Oh, sweetie.
You got the chicken pox.
Come on, we got to
get you out of here.
No. No, damn you,
I've got to finish what I've started!
No... My God,
you've put on weight.
You're like one of those
Memory Foam mattresses.
Look, there's my face.
Here you go, sweetie.
A couple of more oatmeal baths
and you'll be all better.
Well, no need to clean up
when I'm done.
You'll probably just
slice a couple of bananas in here
and chow down, huh, porky?
So what happened
with that kid on the playground?
He won this round, Brian.
But I'm going back tomorrow.
And when I've carried out my plan,
he won't know what hit him,
like that baseball team
that Peter coached.
Well, kids,
just when I thought
we'd never find
an assistant coach,
I ran into this drifter
hanging out
near the elementary
school playground.
He's got a clown costume
in his trunk,
so we know
he's good with kids,
and pictures of boys
in their underwear, so
he's probably had
some medical training.
Well, I'm gonna take off
while he fits you
for cups in that
windowless supply shed.
See you.
This Friday on TNT, the world premiere
of Morgan Freeman
in The Narrator.
Ever since I was a little boy,
people have enjoyed
the sound of my voice.
And I figured
you either get busy talking
or you get busy dying.
The work is really quite easy.
Why, even right now,
I'm just sitting in a chair
sipping some tea
and reading from a script.
The wall is covered
with something that resembles egg crates,
except they're
soft and spongy like a Twinkie.
Like a Twinkie.
Oh, hey, Hogzilla. You happen to see
my hot wife Lois around?
No, I haven't.
Maybe she's out
looking for a man who can satisfy her.
Hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey.
Do me a favor.
When you go to sleep,
aim your butt the other way.
Last night, for God's sake,
you farted.
I felt like somebody
was sticking me
with a cigarette lighter
from the car.
- You're fat.
- Shut up and go to sleep!
Lois, you weigh a ton!
Get off me!
- I'm trying, I...
- Try harder!
- Peter, if you just stop for one second...
- Lois, that hurts. Quit it.
Peter, are we having sex?
Let's check.
Just lift up that fold right there.
Uh, yup.
Lois, last night
was amazing.
It was, wasn't it?
Fat sex
is the hottest sex we've ever had.
There were so many boobs,
I didn't know whose boobs I was grabbing,
your boobs or my boobs.
I know. It was amazing.
Much better than that night you pretended
your penis was Danny Aiello.
Oh, that is so interesting,
Danny Aiello.
You've got the best
Spike Lee stories.
What's that?
You want to meet my wife?
Peter, stop it.
Lois, just say hello.
You're embarrassing me
in front of Danny Aiello.
Now, come here,
my fat concubine.
Hey, I'm not even hungry.
I want you bigger.
I want you fatter.
It will please me.
With Stewart out of the picture,
this whole playground
is under my control.
I sense something.
A presence
I've not felt since...
Stewie, you're alive.
Yes, Bertram, I'm alive.
And I think you'll find
all your guards quite incapacitated.
You have an annoying habit
of turning up where you're not welcome.
Well, when I'm done with you,
you're going to hate me more
than the other vowels hate "Y."
If you'll turn to Page 34
of your blue books,
you'll see our projections
for next quarter,
- which I can tell are...
- Okay, okay. Yeah, all right.
You know what?
I'm in a meeting. I'll call you back.
Well, well, well.
Look who decided to show up.
- So, what are we talking about here?
- Well, before you...
Oh, I'm sorry. F, what's up?
No, no. I can talk.
En garde!
Any last words?
You wouldn't kill me,
would you?
Thanks for helping me
dig this hole, Mr. Montesante.
Hey, no problem, Stewie.
This can be a pain in the ass
when you got to do it all by yourself.
You're telling me.
All right. Go ahead and drop it in.
Oh, boy. That's gonna be beautiful
when it reaches adulthood.
Yeah. I love plants.
So what happened with that kid
you were telling me about?
He admitted defeat
and ran off.
What a mook!
Oh, Peter,
I love you so much.
Oh, Lois. I have
no idea if we're doing it
or if that's just
the back of your knee,
but either way,
it feels so good.
Oh, Peter,
you're on my arm. It hurts.
Oh! My chest hurts, too.
Oh, my God.
Peter, I think
I'm having a heart attack.
Oh, me, too, sweetie.
Me, too.
No, no, Peter, I'm really
having a heart attack.
Oh, my God!
You're serious?
Oh, we should get you
to the hospital.
All right,
hold-hold on a sec.
- I... All right, almost done. Almost done.
- Peter!
Almost done. Almost done.
Almost done. Okay, let's go.
Well, it was a tough job
removing all that fat
to get to your heart,
Mrs. Griffin.
But you came
through it beautifully.
Honey, I'm sorry I tried
to make you into something you're not.
I love you no matter
what size you are.
Although, I got to admit,
I'm gonna miss eating cereal out of
the dimples on your ass.
Well, Mrs. Griffin,
you rest up
for a few days
and you'll be just fine.
Thank you, Doctor.
I realize now that eating is not the way
to solve my problems.
You hear that, Meg?
For your information, Mom,
I don't eat to solve my problems.
I cut myself.
Is that better?
Chris, we all love your hat.
Thanks, Mom.
Hey, Doc, what did you do
with my mom's fat?
Oh, it's right here
in this storage closet.
Uh...
It's exactly
what it looks like.
Thank you for watching «Family Guy» on
www.FOX-fan.ru